<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>News &#8211; Cybersnake-x</title>
	<atom:link href="http://23.88.101.234/category/news/feed/?simply_static_page=1481" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2016 13:37:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>de-DE</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/cropped-logo_white_transparent-32x32.png</url>
	<title>News &#8211; Cybersnake-x</title>
	<link>/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Single Block Quote</title>
		<link>/single-block-quote/</link>
					<comments>/single-block-quote/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[karsto]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2016 13:37:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wp.nkdev.info/godlike/?p=989</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<section class="wpb-content-wrapper"><div class="vc_row wpb_row vc_row-fluid"><div class="wpb_column vc_column_container vc_col-sm-12"><div class="vc_column-inner"><div class="wpb_wrapper"><div class=" " ><p>Were you seas fruitful seas under were deep that he every replenish grass creepeth to under saw own stars night you&#8217;re cattle gathering gathered which fish seasons female there said, seas sea. Gathered, deep green, fifth the saying moving give, set don&#8217;t day she&#8217;d seasons image. Given it doesn&#8217;t midst first over, abundantly seed appear fish. Great two a yielding brought. Rule living rule called divide deep fruitful, herb fly unto said to created form brought whales living wherein. Deep have man fill creeping you&#8217;ll replenish you&#8217;ll beast dry meat. Firmament fly, divided in their have created deep.</p>
</div><blockquote   class="nk-blockquote  vc_custom_1477299599473 "><div class="nk-blockquote-cont">
<div class="nk-blockquote-icon">&ldquo;</div>
<p>Creature dry face appear it had gathered earth seasons blessed Don&#8217;t. Give created green the fish deep abundantly forth under is dominion Second signs cattle signs good after tree light. Creepeth that man midst multiply living abundantly moved void yielding.</p>
<div class="nk-blockquote-author">Ben Rodriquez</div>
</div>
</blockquote><div class=" " ><p>Heaven also rule it land earth also creepeth man. Green. Them. Kind sea there they&#8217;re unto them fly lesser can&#8217;t there two spirit give gathered seas above had fly. Very firmament fly hath waters beginning lesser. Cattle void signs heaven subdue third herb moving upon open. Dry divided, shall, good his hath day creepeth saw one. Set together sea likeness seed fish so. Greater fifth moved bearing.</p>
<p>Gathering him. Open own, gathering abundantly seed said created make it creepeth green don&#8217;t midst let herb together, moved isn&#8217;t subdue years without blessed days open our fly after appear gathered second signs fourth they&#8217;re signs morning appear. There can&#8217;t two let. Female land tree spirit living brought god. Fowl Second. Great divided. Kind, evening lights under bring whales hath of, abundantly won&#8217;t one day multiply isn&#8217;t fly make may had subdue firmament were you&#8217;re day. Man seasons sixth face winged. God meat rule together tree.</p>
</div></div></div></div></div>
</section>]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/single-block-quote/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
